<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steven Lauterwasser</title>
    <link>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Steven Lauterwasser</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 Steven Lauterwasser</copyright><atom:link href="https://stevenlauterwasser.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>I can be contacted via email at swlauterwasser@berkeley.edu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>My CV can be downloaded here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/music/</guid>
      <description>I have been the music director for Perfect Fifth since Fall 2014. Perfect Fifth is a small student a cappella choir specializing in the music of the Renaissance, but our repertoire ranges from the beginnings of western polyphonic music in the Middle Ages all the way to contemporary art music. While it previously relied on directorial support from the University of California Choral Ensembles (ably provided by Mark Sumner), under my tenure Perfect Fifth has shifted to being fully self-run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/research/</guid>
      <description>Strangers in their Own Party: Dissatisfied Partisans and the Worldview Model of Polarization The Republican Party’s rejection of the outcome of the 2020 presidential election is nearly unprecedented in modern American politics, but there is one way that it is unremarkable: it has no Democratic equivalent. Rather, it is only the most extreme example of the apparently asymmetric nature of polarization over the last forty years. However, current work on mass polarization neither captures nor explains this asymmetry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenlauterwasser.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I have extensive experience teaching both within the university and outside of it. I have six years of experience as a Graduate Student Instructor at UC Berkeley, where I received an Outstanding Graduate Student Instructor Award in 2021 and a Certificate of Teaching and Learning in Higher Education. I&amp;rsquo;ve taught sections for a wide variety of courses, from Intro to Sociology and Intro Methods to upper level courses including both those focused on particular topic areas (i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
